DO VUONG PHUC

FULLSTACK ENGINEER • MACHINE LEARNING ENGINEER

(+84) 707 953 475

• HCM City, Ward 16, District 8

■ 16th Oct, 2001

phuc16102001

k phuc16102001

in phuc16102001

ABOUT ME

I am a final-year student at the University of Science, majoring in IT. I am goal-oriented, dedicated to my work, and always open to new experiences, especially those related to my field of study, to enhance my coding practice.

I have gained many from being a leader of group projects, which is why problem-solving, presentation and leadership skills are not weaknesses of mine. I have a strong passion for software engineering and computer science, and I hope I can contribute to the development of society.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

University of Science

Artificial Intelligent major | 2019 - Now

• Bachelor in Information Technology (GPA: 3.93/4)

LANGUAGE

• English: IELTS Academic Certificate 6.5 (B2 level)

SELECTED PROJECTS

Huimitu - Ecommerce website

- Develop an e-commerce website that integrates payment methods (e.g. Momo, Paypal), applies machine learning for the recommendation and visualizes statistics using Tableau.
- **GitHub:** <u>Huimitu repository</u>
- Youtube: Huimitu demonstration
- Website: Huimitu website

Staking DVP Token

- Develop a website for staking a fungible token using NEAR blockchain with Rust programming language.
- GitHub: DVP staking repository
- Website: DVP staking website

Deep Q-learning Snake

- Develop Snake game as an environment to train the DQN model and integrate it with the A* algorithm.
- Achieve the **1st prize** in a university contest
- GitHub: DQN Snake repository

BeeKey

- Apply the Scrum process to develop a freelance platform on the Android operating system.
- **GitHub**: BeeKey repository
- Youtube: BeeKey demonstration

SKILLS

Programming language

• Python, Java, Rust, JavaScript, C++

Software engineering

- Jira, Trello, GitHub, ReactJS, ExpressJS
- Docker, Linux, Postman, Vercel, Heroku
- MSSQL, MySQL, Postgre, MongoDB, Redis

Machine learning

- WEKA, KNIME, Tableau, PowerBI, Sklearn
- HadoopFS, Hive, PySpark, PyTorch, TensorFlow

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Top 1 of class 2019 with the highest GPA
- Scholarship for the excellent student each semester
- Step STEM Alive Singapore 4th Runner-up prize
- 30/4 Olympic contest 2017, 2018 Gold medal

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Software/Data Engineer

Upwork | Nov 2022 - Present

- Develop tools and utilities (e.g. syntax checker, trading probabilistic calculator), analyze data, and build machine learning models
- Job success rate 100%
- **Skill gained:** Be able to work with the foreign clients and enhance software and data skills

Blockchain Developer Intern

VBPO JSC | May 2022 - Oct 2022

- Research blockchain technologies to develop a blockchain-based application for real estate. Full-stack development using NEAR and Aurora Engine
- Skill gained: Understand deeply Bitcoin and its applications and know how to develop smart contracts on NEAR

Mobile Developer

CodeNGreen Ltd | 2019 - 2020

- Develop an Android application for an automatic gardening system
- **Skill gained:** Develop Android application using Java

WORKING REFERENCES

Mr. Kieu My VBPO CTO Phone: (+84) 888 881 081 Mr. Tran Le Hung Phi CodeNGreen CEO Phone: (+84) 937 125 997